// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the maximum number of electrons that can be accommodated in the K shell?",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "2",
      "8",
      "18",
      "32"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which quantum number determines the subshells into which electrons are distributed?",
    answer: "Azimuthal quantum number",
    options: [
      "Principal quantum number",
      "Azimuthal quantum number",
      "Magnetic quantum number",
      "Spin quantum number"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How many electrons can the p subshell accommodate?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "2",
      "6",
      "10",
      "14"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which subshell corresponds to l = 2 in the electron configuration?",
    answer: "d subshell",
    options: [
      "s subshell",
      "p subshell",
      "d subshell",
      "f subshell"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the electron configuration notation for an atom with two electrons in the 1s subshell?",
    answer: "1s2",
    options: [
      "1s2",
      "2s2",
      "2p6",
      "3s2"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many electrons can the 3d subshell accommodate?",
    answer: "10",
    options: [
      "2",
      "6",
      "10",
      "14"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many electrons can the 3d subshell accommodate?",
    answer: "f subshell",
    options: [
      "s subshell",
      "p subshell",
      "d subshell",
      "f subshell"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the maximum number of electrons that can be accommodated in the N shell?",
    answer: "32",
    options: [
      "2",
      "8",
      "18",
      "32"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How many electrons are in the 2p subshell?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "2",
      "6",
      "10",
      "14"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the electron configuration notation for magnesium (atomic number 12)?",
    answer: "1s2 2s2 2p6 3s2",
    options: [
      "What is the electron configuration notation for magnesium (atomic number 12)?",
      "2s2 2p6 3s2",
      "1s2 2s2 2p6",
      "3s2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which is not true about amorphous solids?",
    answer: "Anisotrophic",
    options: [
      "IMF are not equal",
      "Irregular arrangement",
      "Anisotrophic",
      "Shapeless"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 12,
    question: "What is a force within a single molecule?",
    answer: "Intramolecular Forces",
    options: [
      "Net Force",
      "London Bridge Forces",
      "Intramolecular Forces",
      "Negative Force"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Strong Intermolecular forces but Low kinetic energy",
    answer: "Solid",
    options: [
      "Solid",
      "Water",
      "amorphous",
      "Gas"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 14,
    question: "Two or more substance are mixed together to form a solution",
    answer: "Solution",
    options: [
      "Experiment",
      "Goku",
      "Solute",
      "Solution"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What is the substance that dissolves solute?",
    answer: "Solvent",
    options: [
      "Luffy",
      "Solvent",
      "Naruto",
      "bolpen"
    ]
  },
]